our next presenter I guess you could say
if this were a basketball court it would
be game recognizes game and that simply
is the term core of it as the kids say
someone on the same note
who pays their respects to another of
the same grade even how they his virtue
to school by Dan as he's a member of the
class of 2014
symbolizes everything there is about
Northeast Ohio and his Hungarian
heritage I'm just greed some of this
stuff he's a member of the Cleveland
Hungarian Heritage Society United
Hungarian society's Hungarian cultural
center of Northeast Ohio Hungarian
charity ball Cleveland Hungarian
development man and the Hungarian
cultural guard which are beautiful
multi-tier and immaculate so I would
like to when he was going to Catholic
school the school building was very very
very dark didn't have much light
disturbed rats were warm I think that's
when he decided that he wanted to be
and he has many many many awards that he
has received with the beautiful
structures that he has he's the
architect of within the city within the
state and elsewhere the one stands out
to meet with Hungarian cultural gardens
has an organ concert every year tell
Meis in his background
it was the architects of a house that
overlooks Lake Erie and you walk into
this house on the lower level there's a
very wide staircase going into the
second floor the wall is glass on floor
to ceiling when you get to the second
floor there's a very large concert organ
with over 7,600
pipes around you one wall is open
looking over Lake Erie the other three
walls of pipe organs to me with all his
achievements he combined architecture
music and then led him
mother nature through this large window
overlooking Lake Erie
but that said I would love to invite
Richard into the Cleveland Hall of Fame
[Applause]
I mean typically me I don't like people
talk about ideas I live in a million
ideas you just teach routine pragmatic
spiritual life I come back every surface
has brings me back again to be in that
neighborhood
I found elementary love in the thirties
forties I was taught by nuns as the
fifth grade and this man taught me that
openness is more than or goodness is
more than or I have a family magnetic
creative juices we can make this happen
I was there they built the guidance I
was there watching put the stone by
stone picking holes in the ground in
thirds I would you call it me teach you
and me what I brought that to clear my
ideas every seventeen this the letter I
wrote to the gene they taught me my
first week in Athens Greece attention
but I believe in terms of ideas when I
visited satcoms Rome Italy Uranus was
practicing for self-worth coming from
celebration as the music feel the
burning of space the sunlight played
upon the Baroque detail
is probably the most dramatic thing I've
ever seen sumit Chinese do their small
windows and hopes it's not a big deal
the movement of space the plant is a
compliment composite of five holes all
merging into each other that I couldn't
quite understand at all and what is so
small yet there's so much the dump
covers the entire space and no know
where I stood I felt like I was taking
part in the swaying rhythms of
architecture and music great so we just
open this visually but they appreciate
the space and the sound that
reverberates the way we live we preach
not sound isn't it obvious
there were two ticket and organizer as a
piece of art not to talk about it it all
kinds of awards oh I say let's do it
this makes something happen so I'm doing
a book under pretty intense
not the declaration was a proportion of
space many philosophers conscious open
our all those people who talk about the
beauty the definition of beauty have
written about architecture and we don't
even listen
why said why do we have to wait just
nervously classroom why is it part of
our life I'm a missionary I recognize
that if I lose items but if I win I
think we have a serious excitement and
there's a future I hope all of you
understand what the future could be the
future is what we need not analyzing
what we did yesterday but what we put
through tomorrow
[Applause]